<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
     xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
     xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/"
     xmlns:dfpvideo="http://api.google.com/dfpvideo"
     xmlns:tms="http://data.tmsapi.com/v1.1"
     version="2.0">
      <channel>
        <title>ViralBear videos</title>
        <dfpvideo:version>2</dfpvideo:version>        <item>          <media:title>Adorable dogs Mt. Fuji Shiro-nii-san and Kuroo-san having fun in bubble bath</media:title>          <media:description>Bath time is a special bonding moment for dogs, and it's always a joy to watch them have fun in the bubbles. In a recent video shared by @buchrubuchru, we see two adorable pups, Mt. Fuji Shiro-nii-san and Kuroo-san, enjoying their bath time in Tokyo, Japan.

The video starts with Mt. Fuji Shiro-nii-san, the older of the two dogs, leisurely relaxing in the tub while the bubbles gently surround him. It's clear that he truly enjoys his bath time, as he closes his eyes and lets out a contented sigh.

But the younger pup, Kuroo-san, can't help but be envious of his older brother's bubble bath. He desperately wants to join in on the fun and can be seen trying to climb into the tub to join his brother. </media:description>          <media:keywords>dog, animals, pet, bubble, bath, Mt. Fuji, relax, brother, Japan</media:keywords>          <media:city>Tokyo</media:city>          <media:country>Japan</media:country>          <media:category>Animals</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1524</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://youtu.be/Vb8e4dbB-Fw</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 07:42:46 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1524.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1524.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 12:33:36 GMT</dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                  </item>          <item>          <media:title>Incredible shot of lightning captured in Cleveland.</media:title>          <media:description>Nature never fails to amaze us with its powerful and awe-inspiring displays. A recent video captured by @MikeACollier in Cleveland, Ohio, is a perfect example of this. The footage shows an incredible shot of lightning illuminating the dark sky, illuminating the land below in a brilliant burst of light.

The lightning strike is truly spectacular, as it lights up the sky in a beautiful and mesmerizing display. The bright bolts of lightning are clearly visible against the dark clouds, and the way they dance across the sky is truly mesmerizing.

According to @MikeACollier, the lightning was spectacular across the land and he was able to catch this breathtaking video in Cleveland, Ohio. He captured the moment with expertise and skill, capturing the full splendor of the natural phenomenon.

This video is a reminder of the raw power and beauty of nature, and it's a true testament to the skill of @MikeACollier as a videographer. </media:description>          <media:keywords>incredible, lightning, shot, fascinating, land, Cleveland, USA</media:keywords>          <media:city>Cleveland</media:city>          <media:country>Ohio, USA</media:country>          <media:category>Cool</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1522</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4HUBg1NqfS0</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 06:55:28 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1522.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1522.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 12:31:57 GMT</dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                  </item>          <item>          <media:title>The drunk man took revenge on the barrier gate after it hit him!</media:title>          <media:description>The incident took place in the village of Borovlyany near Minsk. The police received information that an unknown person damaged the barrier in the courtyard of the house. Thanks to CCTV cameras, the culprit was found.

It turned out that a drunken 53-year-old man was returning from a friend's house that evening. And when he passed next to the barrier, the device touched him when closing. The man decided to take revenge on the "offender".

First, the man hit the barrier several times and left. But after a while he returned and continued to "beat" the mechanism. In total, more than 20 strikes were made on the device. The damage amounted to about 1000 Belarusian rubles. </media:description>          <media:keywords>drunk, man, barrier, gate, revenge, hit, village, Police, offender, beat, rubles</media:keywords>          <media:city>Borovlyani</media:city>          <media:country>Belarus</media:country>          <media:category>News</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1519</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jV3EFMPC2g4</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 07:07:28 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1519.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1519.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>          <item>          <media:title>A failed group photo and their reaction when the doorbell rang!</media:title>          <media:description>The Author said: "I sat all my pets down to take group pictures, but then the intercom rang, and they all ran to see who it was". Credit to: @7777.pv</media:description>          <media:keywords>cat, dog, animals, pet, group, photo, doorbell, rang, picture</media:keywords>          <media:city>Pavlodar</media:city>          <media:country>Kazakhstan</media:country>          <media:category>Animals</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1517</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/shorts/02WjMLmWQxI</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 06:51:25 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1517.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1517.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>          <item>          <media:title>Dobermann spread the trash all over the house.</media:title>          <media:description>The Author said: "My dog's name is Chivas. He is 1 and 6 months old. Since he was a puppy, he has been a reliable and obedient companion. He enjoys tearing things apart, which is why I always bought him stuff toys. I allow him to tear his toy because he really likes doing it". Credit to: @anna_bersch</media:description>          <media:keywords>dog, Dobermann, animals, pet, trash, house, tear. reliable, stuff toy, puppy</media:keywords>          <media:city>Salihorsk</media:city>          <media:country>Belarus</media:country>          <media:category>Animals</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1515</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/shorts/hsM-dA5tcO0</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 06:41:16 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1515.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1515.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>         <item>          <media:title>The child rubs his dirty shoe into his dad's car compartment.</media:title>          <media:description>The man's patience was put to the test when he saw his son Robert rubbing his shoe against the car compartment. He is trying to calm himself.
 Credit to: @dasha_dasha_sh</media:description>          <media:keywords>child, son, dad, car, dirty, shoe, compartment, rub, patience, calm</media:keywords>          <media:city>Orenburg</media:city>          <media:country>Russia</media:country>          <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1514</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/shorts/DiZ5ELlORY8</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 06:37:31 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1514.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1514.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>         <item>          <media:title>Cute parrot showed off her trick to get her favorite snack!</media:title>          <media:description>The Author said: "My pet is a white-bellied parrot. I have two, whose names are Patch and Yolo. One of my parrots showed off her trick to get her favorite snack, walnuts.
 Credit to: @patchs2yolo</media:description>          <media:keywords>parrot, animals, pet, trick, snack, white-bellied, walnuts, favorite</media:keywords>          <media:city>-</media:city>          <media:country>Korea</media:country>          <media:category>Animals</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1513</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/shorts/m6lEbk73NWI</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 06:32:18 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1513.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1513.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>         <item>          <media:title>A cute Bernese Mountain Dog is scared to be vaccinated.</media:title>          <media:description>The Author said: "My pet's name is Kaia, she is a Bernese Mountain Dog. Kaia was having her vaccine, and she was really nervous. I also posted this video on Tiktok with the caption, "I’m a brave girl. I’m just not crying. Daddy, do something".
 Credit to: @kaia_berneseintw</media:description>          <media:keywords>dog, animals, pet, Bernese Mountain, vaccinated, brave, daddy, Tiktok</media:keywords>          <media:city>-</media:city>          <media:country>Taiwan</media:country>          <media:category>Animals</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1512</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/shorts/RXZhTnZScg8</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 05:23:59 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1512.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1512.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>         <item>          <media:title>Quirky dog drinks water really fast!</media:title>          <media:description>The Author said: "My dog's name is Nori. She is an Italian Greyhound. She's 6 months old and weighs 8 pounds. Extremely funny and quirky, this is just how she drinks water". Credit to: @noritheiggyy</media:description>          <media:keywords>dog, animals, pet, quirky, drink, fast, funny, water, greyhound, USA</media:keywords>          <media:city>San Diego</media:city>          <media:country>California, USA</media:country>          <media:category>Animals</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1511</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/shorts/vQA1W0MLDNM</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 06:21:16 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1511.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1511.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>         <item>          <media:title>A 19-year-old man stole a gift set of products from a store in Russia.</media:title>          <media:description>An unknown person entered the store on Dusi Kovalchuk Street. At first, he just looked at the goods on the shelves. Suddenly, the man grabbed a set of products and ran away. The amount of product that he stole amounted to about six thousand rubles.

The store employee reported the incident to the director, who filed a complaint of robbery on January 7th with the Police Department. On January 13, the suspect was arrested. It turned out to be a 19-year-old resident of the Zaeltsovsky district. The guy has already been prosecuted before. </media:description>          <media:keywords>robbery, stole, store, product, unknown, ran, employee, director, police, arrested</media:keywords>          <media:city>Novosibirsk</media:city>          <media:country>Russia</media:country>          <media:category>News</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1510</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VT727V1FkiQ</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 06:15:56 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1510.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1510.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>         <item>          <media:title>The clingy cat rub against the stranger's head.</media:title>          <media:description>The Author said: "We rented a place in Khvalynsk at the beginning of the year. In the video, I ask my husband to tie my shoelaces when a cat comes and starts rubbing against him. She is very affectionate. When we handed over the keys to the hostess, she stated that the cat belonged to a neighbor, but this was the first time she had witnessed the cat acting in such a manner toward strangers". Credit to: @irina___popova__</media:description>          <media:keywords>cat, animals, pet, clingy, rub, stranger, neighbor, hostess, rent, manner</media:keywords>          <media:city>Khvalynsk</media:city>          <media:country>Russia</media:country>          <media:category>Animals</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1509</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/shorts/WNSmkUg23iQ</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 06:07:56 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1509.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1509.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>         <item>          <media:title>The clever dog knows exactly where to put trash.</media:title>          <media:description>The Author said: "The dog in the video is a Japanese Akita, and I named him Kido. Since he was a child, I've taken care of him. Among my three small dogs, he is the youngest. He can take care of himself. He always looks for the trash can first before taking out the garbage, so he knows which way to walk". Credit to:  @kira.mowgli</media:description>          <media:keywords>dog, animals, pet, clever, trash, Akita, youngest, small, Russia</media:keywords>          <media:city>Zheleznodorozhny, Moscow</media:city>          <media:country>Russia</media:country>          <media:category>Animals</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1508</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/shorts/hDoi7uKqzaI</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 06:03:27 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1508.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1508.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>         <item>          <media:title>The car was driving along the street without a driver!</media:title>          <media:description>People in Baranovichi saw a moving car that didn't have a driver, and they pushed it down the street. It was found out that the car's owner had left it near the store without lifting the handbrake and then gone shopping. Regional traffic police say that he had a remote control in his pocket that he accidentally pressed, which made the car move.

Thankfully, the situation was defused when concerned passersby pulled over the car. No one was hurt, and the cars weren't damaged. The negligent driver has been held accountable by the proper authorities. </media:description>          <media:keywords>car, driver, street, shop, police, control, damage, authorities</media:keywords>          <media:city>Baranovichi</media:city>          <media:country>Belarus</media:country>          <media:category>News</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1507</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8NH9zXvrIqo</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 05:56:03 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1507.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1507.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>          <item>          <media:title>Iranians protest in front of the European Parliament to list the IRGC as a terrorist organization.</media:title>          <media:description>The large and historic gathering of Iranians in front of the European Parliament with the aim of declaring the Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps a terrorist organization by the European Union. 

The Author said: "The national flag of Lion and Sun is as high as the whole world". Credit to: @DariushKoshki</media:description>          <media:keywords>IRGC, terrorist, protest, Iranians, European, Union, flag, Parliament</media:keywords>          <media:city>Strasbourg</media:city>          <media:country>France</media:country>          <media:category>News</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1505</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/shorts/EjBIY55ni_8</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 08:22:22 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1505.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1505.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>         <item>          <media:title>Mobilized soldier sentenced to 5.5 years in prison for beating an officer in Russia</media:title>          <media:description>The Odintsovo garrison military court detained serviceman Alexander Leshkov for beating an officer in Patriot Park. According to the sources, the court sentenced Alexander Leshkov to 5 years and 6 months in prison to be served in a strict regime colony. Leshkov was found guilty of beating his superior during the performance of military service duties during the period of mobilization. </media:description>          <media:keywords>mobilized, soldier, beating, sentenced, military, court, officer, colony, Russia</media:keywords>          <media:city>Moscow</media:city>          <media:country>Russia</media:country>          <media:category>News</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1504</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tepPgV5tXsc</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 08:16:33 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1504.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1504.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 05:10:31 GMT</dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                  </item>         <item>          <media:title>The playful owner teased her cat by biting her!</media:title>          <media:description>The Author said: "My cat's name is Leo, and he is 4 years old. He is a very sweet and charming cat. I always piss her off. Note that no cats were harmed in the making of this video". Credit to: @kingcatleo</media:description>          <media:keywords>cat, animals, pet, bit, playful, sweet, harm, piss</media:keywords>          <media:city>Genoa</media:city>          <media:country>Italy</media:country>          <media:category>Animals</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1503</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/shorts/YpkTLvWdaaI</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 08:10:06 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1503.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1503.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>         <item>          <media:title>The cute husky is digging, and all the mud goes to the dog's face behind her!</media:title>          <media:description>The Author said: "Ponzu, the black dog, is two years old, and Mirin, the red dog is one year old. They are both girls. Ponzu likes digging something, and she often digs anywhere, even at home. When we went to the park that day, Ponzu was happy and excited. She is digging, and all the mud goes to Mirin's face, who is behind her. I don’t know why Mirin kept staying there and being covered with mud. Also, Mirin didn’t know why the mud was coming from the front". Credit to: @tume_ponzu_mirin</media:description>          <media:keywords>dog, animals, pet, husky, dig, mud, park, face, happy, Japan</media:keywords>          <media:city>Minato City</media:city>          <media:country>Tokyo, Japan</media:country>          <media:category>Animals</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1502</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/shorts/2UXu-RIYrXs</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 08:04:39 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1502.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1502.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>         <item>          <media:title>The adorable black cat played the piano and made a creepy sound!</media:title>          <media:description>The Author said: "Our cat actually has a special story. She is a rescue kitten that was brutally attacked as a baby and spent the first part of her life undergoing surgeries to repair her backside. Once we adopted her, she ended up with another serious lung infection that put her in the ICU for a week. Then she got another serious bone infection, and the vet had to remove part of her jaw. She is a true miracle cat. Her name is Black Frances. She is 11 months old and full of attitude. And we call her "one in a million" because her video has gotten more than a million views. She loves playing with our piano and enjoys the sound that she produces". Credit to: @joshuathepost</media:description>          <media:keywords>cat, animals, pet, piano, creepy, play, rescue, vet, sound, ICU, USA</media:keywords>          <media:city>-</media:city>          <media:country>Utah, USA</media:country>          <media:category>Animals</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1501</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/shorts/FkjD5OXuq6c</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 05:38:44 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1501.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1501.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>         <item>          <media:title>A tornado was seen near Atlanta International Airport.</media:title>          <media:description>This video was captured by a citizen inside the airport at Hartsfield-Jackson Atlanta International Airport. According to sources, a flight ground stop has been issued. Credit to: @ddhaacekh</media:description>          <media:keywords>tornado, storm, Airport, citizen, flight, international, Atlanta, USA</media:keywords>          <media:city>Atlanta</media:city>          <media:country>Georgia, USA</media:country>          <media:category>News</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1500</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/shorts/CrGgHOaS8po</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 05:26:29 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1500.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1500.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>         <item>          <media:title>The little boy has a big appetite and eats a lot of rice!</media:title>          <media:description>The Author said: "I recorded this video when he ate at the Tahlilan event where his father passed away. He has an appetite to eat a lot because he's with his friends".
 Credit to: @_maulanaabdilah</media:description>          <media:keywords>little, boy, appetite, big, eat, rice, event, father, passed away, Indonesia</media:keywords>          <media:city>South Kalimantan</media:city>          <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>          <media:category>Cool</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1499</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/shorts/w4zClU1Sizg</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 05:20:17 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1499.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1499.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>         <item>          <media:title>The cute dog is excited to get his gifts!</media:title>          <media:description>The Author said: "My name is Diana Carolina, and my dog's name is Tomas. He is a 3-year-old dog. He is brilliant and loves presents, especially teddies every Christmas he gets one. He also always dresses according to the occasion and in this video, you can see a grinch jersey". Credit to: @tomasito0120</media:description>          <media:keywords>Dog, animals, pet, Christmas, gift, toy, dress, occasion, grinch, Colombia</media:keywords>          <media:city>Bogotá</media:city>          <media:country>Colombia</media:country>          <media:category>Animals</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1498</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kDM3QeBRctM</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 08:29:02 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1498.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1498.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>         <item>          <media:title>Women rallied in Texas regarding the discrimination against female athletes.</media:title>          <media:description>The Author said: "A compelling moment in American sports occurs when athletes present NCAA officials with a petition and a letter threatening legal action against female athletes. The NCAA is not above the law, and policy should be consistent across sports and respect women. It’s the law in the USA not to discriminate based on sex. The NCAA must realize female athletes are going to fight". Credit to: @coachblade</media:description>          <media:keywords>NCAA, athlete, rally, women, discrimination, petition, legal, Texas, USA </media:keywords>          <media:city>-</media:city>          <media:country>Texas, USA</media:country>          <media:category>News</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1497</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GTA3Y3sHdAg</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 04:24:09 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1497.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1497.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>         <item>          <media:title>The skies are red because of the fire at the chemical plant in St. Catharines.</media:title>          <media:description>Residents in St. Catharines were awakened by explosions caused by a chemical spill at Ssonix Products 2010, Inc. For some, the red skies appeared to be an early dawn. According to the St. Catharines fire chief, 54 individuals from surrounding residences were evacuated due to fears of explosions and chemical exposure. The author of this video said, "There was a huge explosion, and when I went outside, the sky turned red". Credit to: @Beatour27</media:description>          <media:keywords>explosion, fire, red, skies, chemical, plant, chief, resident, exposure, Canada</media:keywords>          <media:city>St. Catharines</media:city>          <media:country>Ontario, Canada</media:country>          <media:category>News</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1496</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/shorts/R7a7tOYCRR4</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 04:50:02 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1496.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1496.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>         <item>          <media:title>A man uses paddleboards in the flood area of Goleta.</media:title>          <media:description>The Author said: "My father uses paddleboards in the floods in our neighborhood, claiming that there is no dullness in our community and that he adores Goleta". Credit to: Chelsea Hayes</media:description>          <media:keywords>Paddleboard, flood, area, father, storm, neighborhood, community, adore, USA</media:keywords>          <media:city>Goleta</media:city>          <media:country>California, USA</media:country>          <media:category>News</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1495</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/shorts/q8USdhBt-cs</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 04:44:15 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1495.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1495.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>         <item>          <media:title>Diver was attacked and bit by a triggerfish.</media:title>          <media:description>What happened to the diver was really concerning. They were scuba diving in the Red Sea when a triggerfish appeared and attacked Alex Pikul. He was bitten on the leg. Fortunately, the man is fine. Credit to:  @marhostedtrips</media:description>          <media:keywords>Triggerfish, animals, Red Sea, scuba diving, attack, bit, diver, leg, Egypt</media:keywords>          <media:city>-</media:city>          <media:country>Egypt</media:country>          <media:category>Animals</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1494</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/shorts/pHptrY8PAdQ</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 10:52:15 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1494.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1494.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>         <item>          <media:title>The cat tried the steam heater for the first time and fell in love with it.</media:title>          <media:description>The Author said: "We moved to Genesee in the spring, so this is our first winter in the house. We’ve never had steam heaters before, and the cats really love them. Allistaire is an older cat and very spoiled, and he’s also extra dramatic. He is usually on my lap, but this morning he chose to put his face in the steam. He is healthy and was not pressing his head on the wall. He is fine". Credit to: @tisreese</media:description>          <media:keywords>cat, animals, pet, steam heater, love, winter, spring, morning, dramatic, USA</media:keywords>          <media:city>-</media:city>          <media:country>Colorado, USA</media:country>          <media:category>Animals</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1493</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/shorts/KdwIvND4ovk</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 10:44:07 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1493.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1493.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>         <item>          <media:title>Woman throws shade on the Trump Tower!</media:title>          <media:description>The Author said: "I was on a boat for the architecture tour, waiting for the tour to start, and I saw this woman taking pictures of herself flipping off Trump Tower. I thought it was hilarious so I took a quick video of her". Credit to: @haiter_</media:description>          <media:keywords>woman, Trump, tower, throw, shade, tour, boat, picture, USA</media:keywords>          <media:city>Chicago</media:city>          <media:country>Illinois, USA</media:country>          <media:category>News</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1492</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/shorts/_AREIozptwQ</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 10:39:07 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1492.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1492.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>         <item>          <media:title>The skydiver pulled the parachute way too low!</media:title>          <media:description>The Author said: "I and my seven friends were base jumpers. I was the first to leap and land on the ground. I filmed my friend Theo from the bottom. He deployed his parachute late and just got away with not dying. The man is fine". Credit to: @paragear</media:description>          <media:keywords>skydiver, parachute, friend, low, land, deploy, dying, late, island, Greece</media:keywords>          <media:city>-</media:city>          <media:country>Zakynthos, Greece</media:country>          <media:category>News</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1491</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/shorts/jLszRqHErMw</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 10:31:28 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1491.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1491.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>         <item>          <media:title>The cat went missing and was discovered camouflaged in the carpet.</media:title>          <media:description>The Author said: "I couldn’t find my cat for ages, and then I found him camouflaged in the carpet". Credit to: @tallliiiaaaaaa</media:description>          <media:keywords>cat, pet, animals, missing, camouflaged, carpet, age, Australia</media:keywords>          <media:city>Sydney</media:city>          <media:country> Australia</media:country>          <media:category>Animals</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1490</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/shorts/L8bYU0tCxW0</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 10:27:19 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1490.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1490.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>         <item>          <media:title>Passengers got off the plane due to an FAA system failure.</media:title>          <media:description>The Author said: "Me walking off my plane prior to takeoff, as all our flights have been grounded because of a nationwide FAA air traffic control ground stop because of a system failure. All flights are delayed at least 3 hours". Credit to: @LouMongello</media:description>          <media:keywords>Flights, FAA, failure, plane, passenger, stop, system, control, USA</media:keywords>          <media:city>Orlando</media:city>          <media:country>Florida, USA</media:country>          <media:category>News</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1488</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/shorts/yhTJV0lwx8U</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 06:28:15 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1488.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1488.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>         <item>          <media:title>Neighborhood flooded in Richmond, California</media:title>          <media:description>The Author said: "Flooding on Fordham Ave crossing Rheem Creek upstream of Contra Costa College."
 Credit to: @CitizenRich2</media:description>          <media:keywords>storm, flood, neighborhood, rain, creek, avenue, college, California, USA</media:keywords>          <media:city>Richmond</media:city>          <media:country>California, USA</media:country>          <media:category>Weather</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1487</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rER6Jhdz23I</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 06:22:11 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1487.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1487.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>         <item>          <media:title>The adorable cockatoo enjoys playing the xylophone.</media:title>          <media:description>The Author said: "Bondi is the name of the cockatoo, and he is one and a half years old. He didn't like the instrument at first, but then he started to get interested when I played it a little. He plays when I show an example, but not that much like in the video". Credit to: @bondithecockatoo</media:description>          <media:keywords>cockatoo, animals, pet, adorable, play, instrument, xylophone, enjoy</media:keywords>          <media:city>Helsinki</media:city>          <media:country>Finland</media:country>          <media:category>Animals</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1486</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/shorts/5pfnQ3EmJeQ</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 06:17:39 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1486.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1486.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>         <item>          <media:title>A man got pinched by a giant shrimp on his lip!</media:title>          <media:description>The Author said: "I and my friends were fishing, and we caught a giant shrimp . When my friend was checking the shrimp, it pinched his lip. The man is fine".
 Credit to:  @fahmi_fishing</media:description>          <media:keywords>Shrimp, animals, fishing, pinch, giant, lip, friend, caught. Indonesia</media:keywords>          <media:city>-</media:city>          <media:country>East Java, Indonesia</media:country>          <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1485</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2oLZv0s0-zI</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 07:03:44 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1485.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1485.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>         <item>          <media:title>The fun dog distances herself when her owner coughs!</media:title>          <media:description>The Author said: "My dog's name is Jackie, and she dislikes it when I cough. She finds it very rude, so sometimes I do it just to get a reaction from her. It’s flu season, and Jackie likes to keep her distance when I'm sick". Credit to: @welldamnjackie199</media:description>          <media:keywords>dog, animals, pet, cough, fun, distance, rude, sick, dislike, USA</media:keywords>          <media:city>Rochester</media:city>          <media:country>New York, USA</media:country>          <media:category>Animals</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1484</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/shorts/DUySoxvG7oo</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 06:57:44 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1484.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1484.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>          <item>          <media:title>A large number of disposable vapes were found littered across Dundee.</media:title>          <media:description>The Author said: "In an hour, 55 disposable vapes were discovered littered across Dundee, a distance of 4 miles. #BanDisposableVapes".Credit to: @LessWasteLaura</media:description>          <media:keywords>vapes, disposable, large, litter, mile, discovered, hour, United Kingdom</media:keywords>          <media:city>Dundee</media:city>          <media:country>Scotland, United Kingdom</media:country>          <media:category>News</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1482</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b317aipTQ_w</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 07:45:55 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1482.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1482.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>         <item>          <media:title>A view of a thunderstorm that is expected to produce heavy rain in the Sacramento area.</media:title>          <media:description>The Author said: "Sacramento is seen from the south end of the approaching line, looking west. 7:15 a.m., January 8, 2023".Credit to: @inFLIGHTout</media:description>          <media:keywords>storm, thunder, rain, view, produce, area, west, south, January, California, USA</media:keywords>          <media:city>Sacramento</media:city>          <media:country>California, USA</media:country>          <media:category>Weather</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1481</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rOo2zScTjMs</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 07:38:01 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1481.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1481.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>         <item>          <media:title>Storm coverage: Soquel Creek flooding surges, Capitola Beach's devastation after a storm</media:title>          <media:description>The Author said: "Capitola Police are going door to door, warning of evacuation orders. Soquel Creek is overflowing its banks once more, as is Capitola Beach this morning before high tide".Credit to: @TimmoRice</media:description>          <media:keywords>weather, flood, usa, storm, devastation</media:keywords>          <media:city>Capitola</media:city>          <media:country>USA</media:country>          <media:category>News</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1480</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>-</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 16:56:42 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1480.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1480.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>         <item>          <media:title>Meteor spotted over skies above Sussex overnight</media:title>          <media:description>Amazing video which appears to show meteor blazing over Sheffield.Credit to: @craig_sheff_9</media:description>          <media:keywords>meteor, night, sky, night, uk, Sheffield</media:keywords>          <media:city>Sheffield</media:city>          <media:country>UK</media:country>          <media:category>News</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1479</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>-</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 16:42:41 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1479.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1479.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>         <item>          <media:title>Meteor spotted over skies above Sussex overnight</media:title>          <media:description>Andrew White managed to capture footage of the meteor as it passed over his house in Storrington. Credit to: @andrewawhite</media:description>          <media:keywords>meteor, uk, weather, sky, night, Sussex</media:keywords>          <media:city>Storrington</media:city>          <media:country>UK</media:country>          <media:category>News</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1478</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>-</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 16:27:14 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1478.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1478.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>         <item>          <media:title>The cat went inside the bride's gown!</media:title>          <media:description>The Author said: "This was a wedding expo, it was time for the photo shoot, and suddenly, an uninvited guest came, an orange cat went into the lower skirt of the bride's dress, and I was the one who recorded the video and shouted, "Watch out, there is a cat!"

Credit to: @hadimarvelavenger</media:description>          <media:keywords>cat, animals, pet, bride, gown, wedding, photoshoot, dress, guest, Indonesia</media:keywords>          <media:city>Rangkasbitung</media:city>          <media:country>Java, Indonesia</media:country>          <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1477</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/shorts/_8yZzjHYzd4</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 06:45:33 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1477.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1477.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>         <item>          <media:title>An ex-boyfriend clings to car hood after breaking up.</media:title>          <media:description>The quarrel was noticed by local residents, who filmed the conflict from the balcony of the house. In the video, there's a man who was on the hood of the car, and the rider drives back and forth on the street of Yaroslav Hasek.

According to the sources, the couple broke up after the celebration of the New Year. The guy decided to move out and asked his ex-lover to give him the things that were left in her apartment. In response to a request, she decided to ride him around the yard on the hood. The man is fine.</media:description>          <media:keywords>car, boyfriend, cling, hood, ride, quarrel, local, apartment, Russia</media:keywords>          <media:city>Saint Petersburg</media:city>          <media:country>Russia</media:country>          <media:category>News</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1476</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/shorts/noRGg4bHACY</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 06:38:56 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1476.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1476.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>         <item>          <media:title>A massive amount of snow fell on the two women standing in front of the house!</media:title>          <media:description>This incident occurred in the city of Neftekamsk. A lot of snow fell on the two women who were standing in front of the house. This huge amount fell from the roof of the house's entryway.

In the video, they are waiting at the entrance, and the snow falls. One of them stumbled, and a kind passerby rushed up to help her. Based on sources, they were identifying the women from the video, and they did not seek medical help.</media:description>          <media:keywords>massive, snow, fell, women, house, roof, kind, sources, medical, help, Russia</media:keywords>          <media:city>Neftekamsk</media:city>          <media:country>Russia</media:country>          <media:category>Weather</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1475</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=57DUbYc61nI</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 06:27:46 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1475.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1475.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 06:29:12 GMT</dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                  </item>         <item>          <media:title>The storm wreaked havoc on Soquel Creek</media:title>          <media:description>The storm wreaked havoc on Soquel Creek, which runs swiftly through Capitola Village. Many streets were flooded and destroyed as a result of the bomb cyclone.

Credit to: @NativeSantaCruz</media:description>          <media:keywords>Soquel Creek, storm, bomb cyclone, streets, flood, destroy, California, USA</media:keywords>          <media:city>Capitola</media:city>          <media:country>California, USA</media:country>          <media:category>Weather</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1474</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=o7AccyEp2zw</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 06:15:41 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1474.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1474.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate></dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                </item>         <item>          <media:title>Bomb cyclone caused square waves at Santa Cruz.</media:title>          <media:description>The position of the seas is temporarily lost, and the waves are coming from every direction. Because of the "Bomb Cyclone" that happened in California, the intersection of two seas resulted in square waves.

Credit to: Christopher Lochhead </media:description>          <media:keywords>Bomb cyclone, square waves, seas, storm, intersection, California, USA</media:keywords>          <media:city>Santa Cruz</media:city>          <media:country>California, USA</media:country>          <media:category>Weather</media:category>          <media:filmingDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>          <guid>1473</guid>          <media:youtubeLink>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yIRnfhhs1Nw</media:youtubeLink>          <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 06:10:06 GMT</pubDate>          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1473.jpg" />          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1473.mp4" />          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 06:11:05 GMT</dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>                  </item></channel>
        </rss>